Hi Avanija,

Please use the link provided to download your credentials. The temporary password is set as expired, so you will need to change it before you can connect to the database. You can do this in Oracle SQL Developer with the following steps.

Create New Connection (if you do not have one saved)
1. Click the "+" symbol for a new connection (in the Connections pane on the left side)
2. Enter the details from the file downloaded
        a. Connection Name of your choice
        b. Username
        c. Password
        d. Hostname
        e. Port
        f. Service Name
3. Click Save
        a. Note: You will not be able to "Test" or "Connect" at this point. Your password is expired, you will receive an error with those buttons.
4. Click Cancel

Reset the Password
1. Right-click on the connection (in the Connections pane on the left side)
2. Select "Reset Password..."
3. For "Current Password" enter the temporary password from the file downloaded
4. For "New Password" and "Confirm Password" enter a new password of your choice
5. Click "OK"
6. If you have your password saved in the connection you will need to change that
        a. Right-click on the connection (in the Connections pane on the left side)
        b. Select "Properties"
        c. Enter your new password in the "Password" box
        d. Click "Test" to confirm it works
        e. Click "Save"
7. Double-click the connection to connect and open a new query worksheet


Best regards,

James Lutsey
Database Administrator II
+1 920 751 5440 Direct
+1 920 216 0612 Mobile
